[
    {
        "front": "斯",
        "back": "this, thus, such; to lop off; emphatic particle",
        "pronunciation": "sī",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "党",
        "back": "political party, gang, faction",
        "pronunciation": "dǎng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "陈",
        "back": "exhibit, display; plead; a surname",
        "pronunciation": "chén",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "攻",
        "back": "attack, assault; criticize",
        "pronunciation": "gōng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "苏",
        "back": "",
        "pronunciation": "sū",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "帝",
        "back": "supreme ruler, emperor; god",
        "pronunciation": "dì",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "若",
        "back": "if, supposing, assuming; similar",
        "pronunciation": "ruò",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "波",
        "back": "waves, breakers; undulations",
        "pronunciation": "bō",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "异",
        "back": "different, unusual, strange",
        "pronunciation": "yì",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "策",
        "back": "scheme, plan; to whip; urge",
        "pronunciation": "cè",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "罪",
        "back": "crime, sin, vice; evil; hardship",
        "pronunciation": "zuì",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "州",
        "back": "administrative division, state",
        "pronunciation": "zhōu",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "宗",
        "back": "lineage, ancestry; ancestor, clan",
        "pronunciation": "zōng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "协",
        "back": "be united; cooperate",
        "pronunciation": "xié",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "审",
        "back": "examine, investigate; judge",
        "pronunciation": "shěn",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "皇",
        "back": "royal, imperial; ruler, superior",
        "pronunciation": "huáng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "副",
        "back": "assist; supplement; assistant",
        "pronunciation": "fù",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "抗",
        "back": "resist, oppose, defy, reject",
        "pronunciation": "kàng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "犯",
        "back": "commit crime, violate; criminal",
        "pronunciation": "fàn",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "田",
        "back": "field, arable land, cultivated",
        "pronunciation": "tián",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "央",
        "back": "center, conclude, run out; beg",
        "pronunciation": "yāng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "伯",
        "back": "",
        "pronunciation": "bó",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "监",
        "back": "supervise, control, direct",
        "pronunciation": "jiān",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "露",
        "back": "dew; bare, open, exposed",
        "pronunciation": "lù",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "野",
        "back": "open country, field; wilderness",
        "pronunciation": "yě",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "舰",
        "back": "warship",
        "pronunciation": "jiàn",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "湾",
        "back": "bay, cove, inlet, bend of stream",
        "pronunciation": "wān",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "吉",
        "back": "lucky, propitious, good",
        "pronunciation": "jí",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "剑",
        "back": "sword, dagger, saber",
        "pronunciation": "jiàn",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "亦",
        "back": "also, too; likewise",
        "pronunciation": "yì",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "恩",
        "back": "kindness, mercy, charity",
        "pronunciation": "ēn",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "鲁",
        "back": "foolish, stupid, rash; vulgar",
        "pronunciation": "lǔ",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "端",
        "back": "end, extreme; head; beginning",
        "pronunciation": "duān",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "探",
        "back": "find, locate; search, grope for",
        "pronunciation": "tàn",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "湖",
        "back": "a lake; Hubei, Hunan; bluish-green",
        "pronunciation": "hú",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "予",
        "back": "I, me; to give",
        "pronunciation": "yǔ",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "港",
        "back": "port, harbor; small stream; bay",
        "pronunciation": "gǎng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "额",
        "back": "forehead; tablet, plaque; fixed",
        "pronunciation": "é",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "督",
        "back": "supervise, oversee, direct",
        "pronunciation": "dū",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "泽",
        "back": "marsh, swamp; grace, brilliance",
        "pronunciation": "zé",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "灭",
        "back": "extinguish; wipe out, exterminate",
        "pronunciation": "miè",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "莫",
        "back": "do not, is not, can not; negative",
        "pronunciation": "mò",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "亡",
        "back": "death, destroyed; lose, perish",
        "pronunciation": "wáng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "圣",
        "back": "holy, sacred",
        "pronunciation": "shèng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "诺",
        "back": "promise; assent, approve",
        "pronunciation": "nuò",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "伦",
        "back": "normal human relationships",
        "pronunciation": "lún",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "奥",
        "back": "mysterious, obscure, profound",
        "pronunciation": "ào",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "唐",
        "back": "Tang dynasty; Chinese",
        "pronunciation": "táng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "堂",
        "back": "hall; government office",
        "pronunciation": "táng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "宫",
        "back": "palace",
        "pronunciation": "gōng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "君",
        "back": "sovereign, monarch, ruler, chief, prince",
        "pronunciation": "jūn",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "谋",
        "back": "plan, scheme; strategem",
        "pronunciation": "móu",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "镇",
        "back": "town, market place; suppress",
        "pronunciation": "zhèn",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "凡",
        "back": "all, any, every; ordinary, common",
        "pronunciation": "fán",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "诸",
        "back": "various, all, these; surname",
        "pronunciation": "zhū",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "庄",
        "back": "village, hamlet; villa, manor",
        "pronunciation": "zhuāng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "祖",
        "back": "ancestor, forefather; grandfather",
        "pronunciation": "zǔ",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "暴",
        "back": "violent, brutal, tyrannical",
        "pronunciation": "bào",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "塔",
        "back": "tower, spire, tall building",
        "pronunciation": "tǎ",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "隐",
        "back": "hide, conceal; hidden, secret",
        "pronunciation": "yǐn",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "蒙",
        "back": "cover; ignorant; suffer; mongolia",
        "pronunciation": "méng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "欲",
        "back": "desire, want, long for; intend",
        "pronunciation": "yù",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "遭",
        "back": "come across, meet with, encounter",
        "pronunciation": "zāo",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "徒",
        "back": "disciple, follower; go on foot",
        "pronunciation": "tú",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "姆",
        "back": "",
        "pronunciation": "mǔ",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "曲",
        "back": "crooked, bent; wrong, false",
        "pronunciation": "qū",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "塞",
        "back": "stop up, block, seal, cork; pass, frontier; fortress",
        "pronunciation": "sāi",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "侵",
        "back": "invade, encroach upon, raid",
        "pronunciation": "qīn",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "刑",
        "back": "punishment, penalty; law",
        "pronunciation": "xíng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "谷",
        "back": "valley, gorge, ravine",
        "pronunciation": "gǔ",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "川",
        "back": "stream, river; flow; boil",
        "pronunciation": "chuān",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "潜",
        "back": "hide; hidden, secret, latent",
        "pronunciation": "qián",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "抵",
        "back": "resist, oppose; deny; off-set",
        "pronunciation": "dǐ",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "杰",
        "back": "hero; heroic, outstanding",
        "pronunciation": "jié",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "郑",
        "back": "",
        "pronunciation": "zhèng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "混",
        "back": "to mix, blend, mingle; to bumble along",
        "pronunciation": "hùn",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "臣",
        "back": "minister, statesman, official",
        "pronunciation": "chén",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "雅",
        "back": "elegant, graceful, refined",
        "pronunciation": "yǎ",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "盛",
        "back": "abundant, flourishing; contain; fill",
        "pronunciation": "shèng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "怒",
        "back": "anger, rage, passion; angry",
        "pronunciation": "nù",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "残",
        "back": "injure, spoil; oppress; broken",
        "pronunciation": "cán",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "宇",
        "back": "house; building, structure; eaves",
        "pronunciation": "yǔ",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "猛",
        "back": "violent, savage, cruel; bold",
        "pronunciation": "měng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "毁",
        "back": "destroy",
        "pronunciation": "huǐ",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "盟",
        "back": "swear; oath, covenant, alliance",
        "pronunciation": "méng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "丁",
        "back": "male adult; robust, vigorous; 4th heavenly stem",
        "pronunciation": "dīng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "魔",
        "back": "demon, evil spirits; magic power",
        "pronunciation": "mó",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "沿",
        "back": "follow a course, go along",
        "pronunciation": "yán",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "啦",
        "back": "final particle of assertion",
        "pronunciation": "la",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "瓦",
        "back": "tile; earthenware pottery; girl",
        "pronunciation": "wǎ",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "援",
        "back": "aid, assist; lead; cite",
        "pronunciation": "yuán",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "夺",
        "back": "take by force, rob, snatch",
        "pronunciation": "duó",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "偏",
        "back": "inclined one side; slanting",
        "pronunciation": "piān",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "袭",
        "back": "raid, attack; inherit",
        "pronunciation": "xí",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "侠",
        "back": "chivalrous person; knight-errant",
        "pronunciation": "xiá",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "侧",
        "back": "side; incline, slant, lean",
        "pronunciation": "cè",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "债",
        "back": "debt, loan, liabilities",
        "pronunciation": "zhài",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "融",
        "back": "melt, fuse; blend, harmonize",
        "pronunciation": "róng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "纵",
        "back": "indulge in, give free reign to",
        "pronunciation": "zòng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    },
    {
        "front": "障",
        "back": "separate; shield; barricade",
        "pronunciation": "zhàng",
        "collection_id": "6"
    }
]